Guide to the Reston Reflections oral history collection, 1994-2009
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Reston Reflections oral history collection
1994-2008
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Langston Hughes Middle School
C0171
56.5 linear feet (113 boxes)
The Reston Reflections are a collection of interviews done by the students at Langston Hughes Middle School. The students conducted interviews with residents of Reston to create an oral history of Reston. The project spans several years beginning in 1994 with the final interviews in 2009. Among those interviewed are some of Reston more prominent citizens such as Robert E. Simon, the founder of Reston, and Martha Pennino. The collection is divided into four series, the first contains the transcripts of the interviews, the second series is audiotapes from the interviews, the third is the interviews from 1996 that were originally separated from the majority of the collection and the fourth are the interviews from 2001, 2003 and 2009 that were also separated. The collection is large and contained within 128 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Sarah Larson, Gene B. Zablotney, and others in 1995-2010.
Historical Information
Langston Hughes Middle School is a school in Reston in Fairfax County. The school was named for the poet, Langston Hughes, and was established in 1979. Beginning in 1994 the eighth graders at Langston Hughes Middle School began an oral history project where they interviewed different citizens of Reston. Each year had a different theme starting with Reston's Thirtieth Anniversary (1994-1995), Volunteers in the Community (1996), Leadership in the Community (1998), Business in the Community (1999), Transportation in the Community (2000), Life Cycle of Neighborhoods (2001), Civil Rights Movement (2002), War and the Community (2003), Reston's Fortieth Anniversary (2004), Providing Affordable Housing (2005), Women in Community (2006), Creating Recreation Opportunities in Community (2007) and Technology and Community Change (2008).
Scope and Content
The Reston Reflections are a collection of interviews done by the students at Langston Hughes Middle School. The students conducted interviews with residents of Reston to create an oral history of Reston. The project spans several years beginning in 1994 with the final interviews in 2009. Among those interviewed are some of Reston more prominent citizens such as Robert E. Simon, the founder of Reston, and Martha Pennino.
Series one is titled Transcripts. This series contains the transcripts of the interviews that the student conducted. The transcripts have descriptions of the interviewee, questions and answers from the interviews, report from the student on the process they undertook to arrange the interviews and a final evaluation done by the teacher, grading the students projects. Some of the transcripts also have the audiotapes because the projects have not been processed previously. Also included at the beginning of the series are an index and list of those interviewed. The series is dated from 1994 to 2008 and contained in 79 boxes.
Series two is titled Audiotapes. These are the tapes that have been removed from the transcripts. The tapes are the actual interviews conducted by the students. The audiotapes are from the oral histories that were previously processed and are the earlier interviews done by the students of Langston Hughes Middle Schools. The series is dated from 1994 to 2000 and is contained in 10 boxes.
Series three is titled 1996 Interviews (Volunteers). These are additional transcripts and audiotapes that were done in 1996 by the students at Langston Hughes Middle School. They were originally stored separated under the title oral history in the Planned Community Archives. They are now organized together with the rest of the Reston Reflections. The series is dated 1996 and is contained in 6 boxes.
Series four is titled 2001, 2003 and 2009 Interviews. These are additional transcripts and audiotapes completed by the students at Langston Hughes Middle School. The topics covered are Life Cycle of Neighborhood in 2001 and the War and Community in 2003. They were processed separately but have now been organized with the entire Reston Reflection collection. The series is dated in 2001, 2003 and 2009, and is contained in 33 boxes.
Arrangement
Organized into four series.
Series 1: Transcripts, 1994-2008 (Boxes 1-79)
Series 2: Audiotapes, 1994-2000 (Boxes 80-90)
Series 3: 1996 Interviews (Volunteers), 1996 (Boxes 91-96)
Series 4: 2001, 2003 and 2009 Interviews, 2001, 2003, 2009 (Boxes 97-128)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds many other collections on the history of Reston, Virginia and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Oral history--Virginia--Reston.; Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.
Document Types:
Sound recordings.
Contents List
- Series 1: Transcripts, 1994-2008; (79 boxes)
  The transcripts have descriptions of the interviewee, questions and answers from the interviews, report from the student on the process they undertook to arrange the interviews and a final evaluation done by the teacher, grading the students projects. Some of the transcripts also have the audiotapes because the projects have not been processed previously. Also included at the beginning of the series are an index and list of those interviewed.
  - Brochures, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 1)
    518.22
  - Index, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Index, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - List of Interviewees, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Fragments, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    514.28
  - Odds and Ends, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 6)
    518.23
  - Releases, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    518.25
  - Release Forms, April 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aaron, Barbara, June 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Aaron, Barbara, June 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Veronica, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Abrams, Veronica, May 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Abrams, Veronica, May 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Abrams, Veronica, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ackerman, Patricia Lanka, May 15, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Hebron, December 29, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Adler, Cookie, June 9, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Adler, Cookie, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aguero, Lloyd, April 8, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ahart, Thomas, June 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ahart, Thomas, June 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ahart, Thomas, June 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Albert, Robin, June 2, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Albert, Nellum and Velma, May 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Albright, James, May 29, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Albright, Lola, June 3, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alcorn, Dan, March 24, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Kim, April 20, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Allan, C.W., January 1, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    452.2
  - Allen, Robin, May 16, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    512.02
  - Allen, Susan, June 11, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Susan, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Aloanso, Leo, December 15, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    452.3
  - Alvarez, Carolyn, June 17, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Aman, William, January 24, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    504.1
  - America, Richard, May 19, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - America, Richard, May 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - America, Richard, May 18, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Ames, Priscilla, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 15)
    452.4
  - Ames, Priscilla, January 14, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    504.2
  - Ames, Priscilla, June 10, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ames, Priscilla, May 2, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ames, Priscilla, May 2, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ames, Priscilla, May 3, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Amos, January 2, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    504.3
  - Anderson, George, May 18, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, George, May 18, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Nancy, June 3, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Anselene, Art, May 30, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Anthony, Jane, June 5, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, Jane, June 5, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Appel, Joe, May 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Armstrong, Lou Ann, June 9, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Armstrong, Lou Ann, June 2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Austin-Wooden, Tracy, 2000s (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Averne, Robert, March 20, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    517.27
  - Avjean, Ruth, January 26, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    504.4
  - Bacha, Catherine, June 4, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bailey, Mary, June 6, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ball, Ruth, May 11, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ball, Ruth, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ball, Ruth, 2000s (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Barber, Deborah, January 14, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    504.5
  - Barnum, Barney, May 2, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    518.18
  - Barnum, H.C., May 9, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Barnum, H.C., May 2, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Barokas, Judy, May 2, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Barokas, Judy, May 2, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Baroody, June 9, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    512.03
  - Barrett, Carolyn, May 27, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    518.3
  - Barry, David, May 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Barry, David, June 13, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    512.04
  - Bartelt, Tom, January 12, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    504.6
  - Barton, Martha, January 11, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    504.7
  - Batts, May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Baumgart, Gayle, June 4, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    512.05
  - Beachan, Joan, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Beaver, Barb, May 29, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Becker, Amy, June 4, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Becker, Amy, June 4, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Beecey, Barbara, January 13, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    504.8
  - Becey, Barbara, May 25, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    512.06
  - Beers, Diane, May 1, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Beese Dennis, December 20, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    452.5
  - Behrmann, Art, May 22, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bender, Julie, January 2, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    452.6
  - Bendo, Peter, May 8, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin, Carol, June 1, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    512.07
  - Benishek, Katherine, May 18, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bensigner, Frank, June 6, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bensigner, Frank, January 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    504.9
  - Bentley, Maryanne, June 9, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Beres, Cindy, June 3, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Berger, Joannie, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Berlin, Rena, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bernhardt, May, March 7, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    512.1
  - Berry, Sheila, December 16, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    452.7
  - Bhatnagar, Ramesh, June 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bhatt, Nikandth, January 22, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    504.10
  - Biggs, Dawn, January 12, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    504.11
  - Binder, Pat, December 22, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    452.8
  - Blye, Melissa, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bobzien, David, May 16, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bobizen, David, June 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Bohnslav, Maurine, May 4, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bolle, Rita, May 1, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    516.29
  - Bolton, Janet, December 30, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    452.9
  - Bolton, Vade, December 28, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    452.10
  - Bonner, Ken, January 20, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    504.12
  - Bonner, Ken, April 20, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    517.20
  - Bookbinder, Marquvx, June 16, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Boone, Eileen, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Boster, Gail, December 18, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    452.11
  - Boster, Mark, December 24, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    452.12
  - Boston, Bruce, April 29, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bouie, Bill, April 10, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    515.28
  - Bouie, Bill, May 2, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bouie, Bill, May 5, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bouie, Bill, May 2, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bouie, Bill, January 17, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    504.13
  - Bouwmeester, Paul, June 2, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bowers, Jennifer, June 10, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bowers, Jennifer, June 8, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bowie, December 10, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    452.13
  - Boyd, Margaret, December 29, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    452.14
  - Boyd, Margaret, January 11, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    504.14
  - Boyd, Margaret L., May 20, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Boyd, Margaret, June 12, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Boyd, Margaret, June 12, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Boyer, Kay, May 8, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bradley, Alaka, June 12, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    512.08
  - Bradley, Carol, May 3, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Bradley, Carol, May 3, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Bradley, Carol, May 30, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Bradley, Carol, January 14, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    504.15
  - Bradley, Murray, May 29, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bradshaw, Jan, December 8, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    504.16
  - Braunstein, Leslie, June 4, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    512.09
  - Bredesen, Dorothy, December 4, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    452.15
  - Briggs, Anna C., January 30, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    504.17
  - Brook, Louise, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 7)
    512.10
  - Brown, Don, May 16, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Donald, May 16, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Jean, December 27, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    504.18
  - Brown, Kathy, May 3, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Brownsword, Joanne, 2000s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Brownsword, Joanne, June 0, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Bruce, Carol, May 26, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bruce, Carol, February 11, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    504.19
  - Brutsche, Mark, June 5, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Brutsche, Mark, June 5, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Brunson, Leomia, January 19, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    504.20
  - Brutsche, Karen, April 17, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    516.17
  - Bucheis, Aquina, May 30, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Buchner, Michael, June 8, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Buell, Mark, April 25, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    515.25
  - Bugge, Diana, January 11, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    504.21
  - Bunney, Mark, June 4, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Burd, Joyce, June 8, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Burd, Joyce, 2000s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Burns, Sharon Ann, June 7, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Burns, Sharon, June 7, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Burton, Greg, April 30, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    517.16
  - Burton, Greg, December 21, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    452.16
  - Butcher, 2000s (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Butler, Larry, May 30, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    512.12
  - Butler, Viris, June 3, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    512.11
  - Butler, Larry, May 21, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Butler, Larry, May 31, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Butowsky, Harry, May 23, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Byrne, Eileen, June 9, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cabrera, Estefania and Majorie Alvarez, June 10, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Caggino, Tammy, June 4, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cahill, Steve, June 8, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Calabrese, David A., May 22, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Calbert, Thelma, May 10, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Calbert, Thelma, May 10, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Caldwell, Ronald, June 8, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Calderwood, Kevin, May 20, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Caldwell, Brian, May 24, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    512.13
  - Calilhanna, Marie, April 16, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    518.15
  - Callahan, Dave, January 2, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    452.17
  - Callaghan, John, January 12, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    504.22
  - Camarda, Andy, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 13)
    512.14
  - Camarda, Andrew, December 24, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    452.18
  - Campbell, Carlos, May 7, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Campbell, Marian, December 23, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    452.19
  - Campbell, Carlos, May 7, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Campbell, Gray, January 10, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    504.23
  - Cantwell, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Capabianco, Christine, December 28, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    452.20
  - Carley, Stephanie, January 16, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    504.25
  - Carrigan, Sherry, February 21, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    504.24
  - Carruthers, Linda, June 19, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    517.21
  - Carter, Alonzo, June, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    512.15
  - Carter, Charles, May 17, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Castenton, Elizabeth, 2000s (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Centner, Christopher, May 14, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cheir, Anne, January 16, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    504.26
  - Cherian, Ranjit, May 7, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    504.27
  - Chon, Wendy, May 9, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Christian, Prentince, May 7, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    504.28
  - Christman, Bruce, January 18, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    504.29
  - Chung, Chris, June 12, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ciszek, Kathy, January 1, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    452.21
  - Ciszek, Raymond, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 19)
    452.22
  - Ciszek, Raymond, 2000s (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cleveland, Jim, May 27, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    512.16
  - Cleveland, Karen, June 10, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cleveland, James, May 24, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Cleveland, Karen, June 10, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Clifton, Courtney, May 11, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Clifton, Courtney, May 10, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cockrill, Therese, May 17, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cocomellow, Gina, May 31, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    512.17
  - Cocomello, Gina, April 18, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    516.23
  - Codding, Rosemary, January 15,1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    504.30
  - Cogan, Clip, May 16, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Ivan, May 8, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cole, Ivan, June 9, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    512.18
  - Cole, Helen, May 17, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cole, May 13, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Coleman, Georgette O., May 25, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Collins, Betty, May 9, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Collins, Betty, May 9, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Compton, Karen, May 4, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Conaway, Mary, May 30, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Confer, Ann, May 7, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Conkey, Jack, April 30, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    517.24
  - Conner, Jane, June 6, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Conner, Jane, May 12, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Conrad, Tom, April 14, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    515.20
  - Conyers, Virginia Lynn, December 17, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    452.23
  - Coonin, Tara, June 5, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Coonin, Tara, June 9, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Copeland, Rachel, May 5, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    517.1
  - Corbitt, Rodger, April 23, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    514.4
  - Cordyack, Marianne, April 27, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cordyack, Marianne, April 3, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    515.3
  - Corkey, Laurie, 2000s (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Corkey, Laurie, June 12, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cosham, Ralph, December 4, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    452.24
  - Coshan, Beverly, June 6, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cote, Jackie, April 13, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    515.1
  - Cotton, Dee, June 7, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cotton, Dee, June 8, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cox, 2000s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cox, Heather, June 9, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Peter, January 1, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    452.25
  - Craft, Dawson, January 8, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    452.26
  - Craig, Mary Ellen, April 29, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    518.19
  - Craighill, Sherry, January 17, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    504.31
  - Cramer, Brett, January 15, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    504.32
  - Creadick, Lisa, June 13, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cristofar, Sharron, May 19, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Crowe, Jeff, June 2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Crowe, Jeff, June 7, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    512.19
  - Crutchley, Mike, December 17, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    452.27
  - Cutler, Brian, June 5, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Dadiani, Norma, December 29, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    452.28
  - Dain, Bob, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 1)
    516.19
  - Dale, Diane, April 12, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dale, Diane, April 12, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dale, Diane, April 20, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - D'Alesandro, Thomas, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 4)
    512.20
  - Danaher, Cheri, June 6, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Danaher, Cheri, June 8, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Daugherty, Jeff, May 30, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Karen, January 3, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    504.34
  - Davis, Clarence, May 8, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Neil, May 30, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Clarence, May 8, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Day, Jane, February 28, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    452.29
  - Day-McKnight, Kim, May 13, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Day-McKnight, June 20, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Day-McKnight, Kim, June 8, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Dayton, Anne, June 11, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Dayton, Anne, June 11, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Dearborn, June 2, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    512.21
  - DeCola, Freya, April 30, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - DeCola, Lee, May 7, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - DeCola, Freya, 2000s (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - DeCola, Lee, May 7, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Decou, Nancy, December 11, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    452.30
  - Dettoratiis, Karen, May 6, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - de la Fey, Frank, May 19, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - de la Fe, Sarah Ann, May 25, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - de la Fe, Sarah Anne, May 6, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - de la Fe, Sarah Anne, 2000s (Box 17, Folder 11)
    512.5
  - de la Fe, Mary, January 17, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    504.36
  - de la Fe, Sarah Ann, June 11, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - de la Fe, Sarah Ann, June 11, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - de la Fe, Sara, June 4, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    512.27
  - Dellagiarino, Margie, December 28, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    452.31
  - DeNoyer, John, January 9, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    504.38
  - DeNoyer, John and Ann Csonka, January 6, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    504.37
  - Deschamps, Ann, May 21, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - DeWerter, Cheryl, June 4, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - DiCarlo, Sally, June 6, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dick, Jeff, June 3, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, A.B., June 23, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dills, Gary, April 11, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    515.30
  - Dipaola, Anthony, April 14, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    516.28
  - Dix, Bob, December 30, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    452.32
  - Dix, Robert, January 5, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    504.39
  - Dobberfuhl, Gail, January 9, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    504.40
  - Doe, Elizabeth, May 13, 12002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Dohman, Eileen, January 19, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    504.41
  - Donatuti, Pauline, December 21, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    452.33
  - Donohue, Tim, 2000s (Box 18, Folder 12)
    512.22
  - Downer, Richard, June 5, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    512.23
  - Downer, Richard, January 9, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    504.42
  - Doyle, Stephen, June 1, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Drum, Mary, June 3, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Drury, Janet, February 23, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    504.43
  - Drury, Buzz, May 11, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Dudek, Henrietta, May 6, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Duman, 2000s (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Dumon, Gene, May 15, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Durkin, Carolyn, May 4, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dwight, Margaret, April 14, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    515.7
  - Dyland, Evans, June 1, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Eastlake, Robin, May 17, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Eastlake, Robin, June 18, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Edwards, Abbie, June 7, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Edwards, Abigail, June 5, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 10)